It's no secret that in order for your app to be successful,
这不是什么秘密 成功的应用
the user has to run it, and for it continue to provide value,
必须要有用户，然而 为了不断地创造价值
sometimes it needs to keep running.
有时需要让应用持续运行
This is tough to do when the phone is asleep.
这并不容易 当手机休眠的时候
I mean, what are you going to do, wake up the phone
我想说的是 你该怎么办呢？
and do the work even though it's already sleeping?
唤醒电话进行工作吗？ 即使已经休眠了？
Well yes, of course, but be careful here because there's
嗯是的，必须的 不过要小心
a large battery problem waiting to happen.
电量会是个大麻烦
My name is Colt McAnlis, and disturbing your phone's beauty
我叫 Colt McAnlis. 打扰你的手机的美容觉
sleep is one of the biggest causes of unneeded battery
在 Android 设备上 是造成不必要的耗电的罪魁祸首之一
drain on Android, but with a few simple changes
不过，稍微改变一下工作方式
to how you're working, you can achieve the same results
你可以取得相同的结果
with less battery problems.
同时减少电量消耗
To illustrate this point, let's talk about my good friend Rado.
为了形象一点 我们来聊聊我的好朋友 Reto
He's an avid social user and a game player,
他是一个狂热的社交用户和游戏玩家
which means his running applications are constantly
就是说 他常用的应用都在不停地
checking scoreboards, uploading photos, and pulling down
检查排行榜 上传照片
the latest hashtag crazes, but they
下载最新的热门标签
do this even when Rado has put his phone to sleep, which
即使 Reto 让他的手机休眠
means by lunch, his phone is already out of battery.
到吃午饭的时候 他的手机已经没电了
Rado has to constantly recharge his phone
Reto 必须经常给他的手机充电
because it suffers from sleep deprivation.
因为他的手机睡眠不足
That is, because these applications are constantly
就是说 因为这些应用程序
waking up the phone, they're eating up battery life
不断地唤醒手机 消耗电量
instead of letting his phone sleep, and sleep is important.
他的手机得不到休眠 而休眠是重要的
Remember that Android will turn off
请记住 Android 会关闭
various parts of your hardware in order
各种硬件部件
to prolong battery life.
以延长电池寿命
First, the screen will dim, followed by it eventually
首先，屏幕会变暗 然后关闭
turning off, and finally, the CPU
最后，CPU 进入睡眠
will go to sleep, all in an attempt to save precious,
所有的一切是为了保存宝贵的
precious battery.
宝贵的电量
But even in this inactive state, most apps will try to do work,
但即使处在这种非活动状态 很多应用会尝试进行工作
and they will have to wake up the phone to do so.
他们将不得不唤醒手机
Now, the easiest way for an app to wake up your phone
对于一个应用 唤醒你的手机
to do work is with the PowerManager.Wakelock API,
进行工作的最简单的方法是调用 API PowerManager.Wakelock
which is used to keep the CPU running
这可以用来保持 CPU 运行
and prevent the screen from dimming or turning off.
和防止屏幕变暗或关闭
This allows your phone to do things like wake
这使您的手机可以做一些事情
up at some future point, do some work,
例如到某个时间醒过来 做一些工作
and then let the phone go back to sleep.
然后再让手机回去睡觉
But see, it's that last part that's the tricky one.
但是，就是最后那一部分最麻烦
See, acquiring Wakelock is actually really easy,
你看，获取 Wakelock 其实很容易
but knowing how to release it is more problematic.
如何释放才是问题
There's lots of ways that this can go horribly wrong.
很多种可能会导致严重错误
What if your application takes 60 minutes instead
出现这样的情况怎么办 如果你的应用需要60分钟
of the expected 10 seconds it takes
而不是所期望的10秒钟
to analyze some image before uploading it to the server?
来分析一些图像 然后再上传服务器
Or what if the server crashes and you never
或者，出现那样的情况怎么办 如果服务器崩溃
get a response from your social media ping,
导致你 ping 社交媒体 却收不到响应
and you end up waiting forever for a result?
最后永远等不到一个结果
The end result is the phone never sleeps and chews
最终结果是手机无法休眠 耗尽电量
through your battery, which is exactly why you should be using
这也正是为什么要使用
the version of wakelock.acquire that takes a timeout parameter.
带超时参数的 wakelock.acquire
This will force the Wakelock to be released
这将迫使 Wakelock 得到释放
after a certain amount of time just in case one of these edge
在指定的时间之后 以防出现
cases actually happens.
类似的特殊情况
But this won't actually solve the problem fully.
但是，这并不能完全解决问题
I mean, what should you set the timeout value to be,
就是说 超时该设置为多少
or how long should you wait before trying to do it again
或者，该等多久 然后再重试
in case you actually fail the first time?
一旦第一次尝试失败
The right solution to this might be to use inexact timers.
正确的解决方案 似乎是使用非精确定时器
See, normally, you set some future date for your event
通常，你设置一个未来的时间
to kick off and wake up the phone,
来触发你的事件 并唤醒手机
but it might be better to change that timing
但更好的做法可能是 选择不同的时机
in order to conserve battery.
以便节省电量
For example, if there's another application that
举个例子 如果另一个应用程序
needs to wake up five minutes after yours has requested to,
需要比你的 晚五分钟唤醒手机
it's optimal to wait for that one
最好能等到那时
to happen so that you can bundle the work together.
这样就可以把工作 集中在一起做
This is at the core of what inexact timers do.
这就是非精确 定时器的工作原理
You can schedule some work for the future,
您可以为将来 安排一些工作
but if the system detects that there's a better time,
但是，如果系统检测到 一个更好的时间
it can delay your work in order to save battery.
就可以推迟你的工作 以节省电量
And in reality, there's a whole group of other situations
而在现实中 还有另外的一大类场景
that might be better to do battery intensive work,
对于耗电量大的工作来说 最佳时机是
for example, when the phone is charging or connected to Wi-Fi
例如，当手机正在充电 或者连接到 Wi-Fi
or already woken up by another process.
或者已经被另一个进程唤醒
If any of your work can be deferred to a future date
如果您的工作可以 推迟到将来的一个时间
when these conditions might be ideal,
当这些条件 比较理想的时候
then you can help improve battery life significantly.
那就可以显著地 延长电池寿命
This is exactly what the JobScheduler API is for.
JobScheduler API 正是用来做这个的
See, this API is perfect to schedule some future work
你看，这个 API 最适合用来 安排某些工作在未来执行
to wait for various combinations of these better conditions,
以获得各种 理想的条件组合
for example, waiting until the unit is plugged in,
例如，等到设备充电
waiting until you're on Wi-Fi, or batching
等到连上 Wi-Fi
a bunch of these tasks together at once.
或者把任务集中起来 批量执行
Basically, with one simple API, you
基本上，通过一个简单的 API
get all that scheduling for free.
你可以免费获得 所有的调度算法
And don't forget with the new revamped battery usage details
还有，别忘了自从手机上有了 新的电量使用报告
on the phone, users now have the ability
现在用户可以看到
to see how long your app is keeping their phone awake for
你的应用让他们的手机 醒了多长时间
and even have the ability to uninstall it
并且可以卸载你的应用
right from the same screen, which means you should probably
就从同一个屏幕上 这意味着你应该
take a few extra minutes and make sure
多花几分钟时间
that all of your wakelock logic is in order using the Battery
通过 Battery Historian 工具来确保所有的 wakelock 逻辑秩序井然
This tool rolled out with the L release of Android
该工具是和 Android L 一起发布的
and can help you understand how often wakes are kicked off,
可以用来了解 唤醒的频率
who initialized them, and how long they lasted,
谁发起的 持续了多久
all in a nice visual package.
一目了然
With these new tools and APIs, you can finally give that sleep
有了这些新工具和 API 你终于可以
deprived phone some well deserved rest.
给缺乏睡眠的手机 一些应得的休息了
But of course, if you would like to avoid sleeping,
不过，如果是你 还不想睡觉
then check out the rest of the Android Performance Patterns
那就去看看 Andr​​oid 性能模式系列的其他短片
resources and don't forget to join our Google+ community
还有，别忘了加入 我们的 Google+ 社区
So keep calm, profile your code, and always remember
保持冷静，分析你的代码 并永远记住
perf matters.
性能攸关
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]